Guide to the Records of the Office of Media Production RG.7.3.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Projects
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reel 107, 277), 2002 November 1 (Box 194, Folder Project 226)
  - Frank McCourt Documentary (Reel 15), 2000 November 20 (Box 194, Folder Project 269)
  - Commencement 2002 (Box 194, Folder Project 352)
  - Gallatin: On the Cutting Edge (Reel 5), Undated (Box 194, Folder Project 366)
  - Stern Undergraduate Recruitment Video 2004 (Reel 35) (Box 194, Folder Project 406)
  - National Geographic - Global Public Health (Reel 38-39), Undated (Box 194, Folder Project 441)
  - Stern MBA Admissions Video 2005 (Reel 1) (Box 194, Folder Project 445)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary, Interview with John Sexton, 2006 October 30 (Box 194, Folder Project 490)
  - Stern Undergraduate Recruitment Video 2006/2007 (Box 194, Folder Project 501)
  - Columbia University: A Celebration (Reel 1-2), Undated (Box 194, Folder Project 514)
  - Genomics Building Campaign Video, Undated (Box 194, Folder Project 541)
  - Dr. J. Fred MacDonald Videos (Reels 1-6), Undated (Box 194, Folder Project 608)
  - Project 0206 (Box 194, Folder Project 0206)
  - Stock Archival Footage - Historic Films (Reel 1), 2006 September 13 (Box 194, Folder Project 609)
  - Naomi Levine's Seminar on Philanthropy and Fundraising (Reels 1-10), 2003 July (Box 195, Folder Project 318)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 (Reel 19), 2008 March 4 (Box 196, Folder Project 548)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement Video 2008 (Reel 1, 2, 5, 8, 10-12), 2008 March (Box 196, Folder Project 569)
  - Stern Undergraduate Footage 2008-2009 (Reel 4-16, 43- photos) (Box 196, Folder Project 593)
  - End of Campaign Video (Reel 1-6, 12-17, 22-27, 39, 53-55), 2008 April - 2008 June (Box 197, Folder Project 572)
  - Genomics Building Campaign Video (Reels 3, 4, 18), 2007 July - 2007 September (Box 197, Folder Project 541)
  - Dr. Amr Moursi - Pediatric Dentistry Media Training (Reels 2-3), 2007 August 16 (Box 197, Folder Project 547)
  - College of Dentistry Honduras Outreach Program (Reels 4-5), 2008 June 18 (Box 197, Folder Project 579)
  - Alaska Dental School Project (Reels 3-4), 2008 February 21 (Box 197, Folder Project 571)
  - TSOA Gala 2005 (Box 197, Folder Project 461)
  - NYU On the Air, 1999 (Box 197, Folder Project 193)
  - University Athletic Association 10th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 197, Folder Project 141)
  - TSOA Salute 2000, 2000 May (Box 197, Folder Project 237)
  - NYU Student Experience (Reels 1-4, 8-16, 21-44, 49-62, 67-87), 2003 (Box 198, Folder Project 375)
  - Stern MBA PreCommencement 2008 (Reels 6-10, 15-18, 20-23, 45, 46) (Box 199, Folder Project 548)
  - Stern Undergraduate Dean Blount Lynon Interview (Reels 1-4), 2008 April 30 (Box 199, Folder Project 574)
  - Elder Mistreatment Video (Reels 1, 3, 4, 8, 10-13, 21), 2008-2009 (Box 199, Folder Project 587)
  - Stern Langone Program Video (Reels 1, 2, 6), 2008 March 26 (Box 199, Folder Project 576)
  - Casa Italiana Documentary Credits, 2000 March (Box 199, Folder Project 248)
  - International Student Film Festival, 1998 February (Box 199, Folder Project 171)
  - NYU Downtown Hospital Video, 1998 (Box 199, Folder Project 91)
  - Dean Daly Tribute Video - With Credits, 2002 May (Box 199, Folder Project 351)
  - Grey Art Gallery/Shisedo Makeup Video, 2000 September (Box 199, Folder Project 239)
  - Stern Undergraduate Recruitment, 1999 (Box 200, Folder Project 215)
  - Stern Public Affairs B-Roll, 2000 July (Box 200, Folder Project 228)
  - Stern in the News 2, Undated (Box 200, Folder Project 302)
  - Stern in the News 3, Undated (Box 200, Folder Project 303)
  - Stern MBA Pre-Term 1999, 1999 August (Box 200, Folder Project 304)
  - Stern on the Air 1998-Founders' (Box 200, Folder Project 307)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Salute, 2001 May (Box 200, Folder Project 309)
  - Brennan Center Video, 2001 September (Box 200, Folder Project 314)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards (Reel 17, 19, 21, 25), 2001 (Box 200, Folder Project 315)
  - NYU on the Air, 2002 April (Box 200, Folder Project 338)
  - NYU Trustees' Trip Florence Madrid, 2002 February (Box 200, Folder Project 339)
  - Weinfeld Gala, 2002 April (Box 200, Folder Project 341)
  - Installation Video for Action Dinner, 2003 January (Box 200, Folder Project 373)
  - Gallatin 30th Anniversary Video, 2003 May (Box 200, Folder Project 374)
  - Ireland House Documentary (Master 1, Reel 12, 13, 18-20), 2005 (Box 200, Folder Project 410)
  - Dean Choi Tribute, 2004 May (Box 200, Folder Project 413)
  - Law School New Building, 2002 (Box 200, Folder Project 283)
  - Leadership University for the New Millenium, 2002 (Box 200, Folder Project 356)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary (Audio Cassette Tapes 3,4,24-34,43-46,48-50,57,59,63,64,67,81-83,92-96,102-106,131,140,141,167) (Box 201, Folder Project 490)
  - Genomics Building Campaign Video (Audio Cassette Tapes 6-9), 2007 July 17 (Box 201, Folder Project 541)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 (Audio Cassette Tapes 24-42,50,51), 2008 March (Box 201, Folder Project 548)
  - Global Network University Video (Audio Cassette Tapes 30-34,38), 2008 March-April (Box 201, Folder Project 559)
  - Lukas Haynes Presentation (Audio Cassette 4), 2008 June 19 (Box 201, Folder Project 570)
  - End of Campaign Video (7-8,28-33), 2008 April (Box 201, Folder Project 572)
  - Dean Tom Cooley Blog Project (Audio Cassette Tapes 3), 2008 April 14 (Box 201, Folder Project 573)
  - Stern Langone Program Video (Audio Cassette Tapes 3-5), 2008 April 36 (Box 201, Folder Project 576)
  - Elder Mistreatment (Audio Cassette Tapes 2,9), 2008 (Box 201, Folder Project 587)
  - NYU Stern Undergraduate Recruitment, 2008 (Box 201, Folder Project 593)
  - NYU College of Dentistry Interviews (Nicaragua), 2008 December (Box 201, Folder Project 600)
  - NYU College of Dentistry Interviews (Hudson, NY), 2008 December (Box 201, Folder Project 606)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi (Audio Cassette Tapes 20-23.33.34), 2008-2009 (Box 201, Folder Project 613)
  - Speeches of Mayor Robert F. Wagner of New York City (Reels 289-306), 1953-1965 (Box 202, File Project 226)
  - Lisa Goldberg Memorial DVD, 2007 February (Box 202, Folder data_value_missing_d0a34188e75f44b78c6c1d264f2d7a98)
  - Master of Science in Digital Imaging and Design, Admissions Pamphlet, circa 2010 (Box 202, Folder data_value_missing_07d77abf3f0c78e5a5b1c749a5fb474d)
  - Bobby Wagner Time Period Binder (Box 203, Folder Project 0226)
  - Photos from the New York City Department of Records and Archives Binder (Box 203, Folder Project 0226)
  - Mayor Wagner's Time Period Binder (Box 203, Folder Project 0226)
  - Pending Wagner Binder (Box 203, Folder Project 0226)
  - Wagner Photographic Stills (Reels 214-219, 231, 232, 253, 263, 264, 269), 2003 (Box 203, Folder Project 0226)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary (Reels 1, 2, 5, 6, 9-13, 15-18, 22, 36,37, 38, 47, 51, 52, 58, 60, 61, 62, 86-91, 97, 98, 99, 100, 101, 118, 132-136, 2006-2007 (Box 204, Folder Project 0490)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary (Reels 68, 71, 73, 74, 112, 118, 119-126, 129, 130, 137-139, 149-156, 159, 160, 162, 166), 2006-2007 (Box 205, Folder Project 0490)
  - Library of Congress "The Life of the City: Films of New York" (Box 206)
  - "Seedy NYC Scenes", 1969, 1973 (Box 205)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 114-117), 2002 (Box 205, Folder Project # 0226)
  - NYU Exteriors: Arch, Park, Library (project unknown), 2009 June 30; 1 Betacam_SP; Video: 1/2" BetacamSP (Box 205, Reel 1)
  - 175th Anniversary: B-Roll (City and Miscellaneous) and McCourt (video clips from Phil Gallo), undated; 1 DVD-R (Box 205)
  - Undergraduate Admission Diversity Book Video (Reel 2), 2005 (Box 205, Folder Project # 0473)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video ( Reel 4), 2007 (Box 205, Folder Project # 0498)
  - Development Campaign Video (Reels 1, 23), 2004 (Box 205, Folder Project # 0420)
  - The Wagners: A Legacy of Public Service (Reels 112 and 113) (Box 206, Folder Project #226)
  - Development Campaign Video: Audio for Interviews (Reels 3, 10, 13, 21, 22, 33, 44, 45), 2004 (Box 206, Folder Project: 0420)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary (Project 0490), 14 April 2008; 6 Betacam_SP
    - Stock Footage Master, 14 April 2008; New York University. Office of Media Production; 1 Betacam_SP; NYU Media Production Label. Previous Unique ID: 0490-169 (Box 205)
      Statue of Liberty (New York, N.Y.); New York University
    - INTV - Courtney Sale Ross, 30 October 2006; 1 Betacam_SP (Box 205)
      Scope and content
      Tape labeled Tape #3.
      Ross, Courtney
    - Sexton last set, 103-213, undated; 1 Betacam_SP (Box 205)
      Sexton, John Edward, 1942-
    - The Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson, 27 November 1972; 1 Betacam_SP; NYU Media Production Label. Previous Unique ID: 0490-176, (Box 205)
      This recording contains only the opening monologue of this episode.
    - Clean NYC 80s-90s (stock footage), April 14, 2008; 1 Betacam_SP; NYU Media Production Label. Previous Unique ID: 0490-168, NYU 175 (Box 205)
    - Robby Benson VO (Reel 1 of 2), November 01, 2006; 1 Betacam_SP (Box 205)
  - Dedication of L. Jay Oliva Teatrino, Villa La Pietra, October 10, 2014; 1 DVD-R (Box 205)
  - NYU Salutes Martin Lipton (Law '55) (2 copies), Probably 2015; 2 DVD-R (Box 206)
  - John Brademas 80th Birthday Celebration (3 DVD Masters) (Box 206, Item Project 524)
  - Mr. Brademas Goes to Washington, 1 DVD (Box 206)
- Series II: 2025 Accretion, 2001-2010; 5 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons; 118 Betacam_SP
  This accretion includes Betacam tapes of NYU events and promotional videos.
  This accretion has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - La Pietra Video / Protection Master with Ferragamo Intro -- Project #0007 -- Reel #169, undated; cuid19169 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19169)
  - NYU B-ROLL - 2001, Material outdated due to WTC, Loeb Student Center -- Project #0059, 2001-09-01; cuid19170 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19170)
  - NYU B-ROLL - Kimmel Center, Tisch, Gallatin, Washington Square Park Exteriors -- Project #0059 -- Reel #11, 2004-04-22; cuid19171 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19171)
  - NYU B Roll / NYU Buildings- Palladium, Furman Hall, Kimmel Center -- Project #0059 -- Reel #12, 2004-06-02; cuid19172 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19172)
  - Stern Public Affairs BRoll -- Project #0228, 2000; cuid19173 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19173)
  - Stern Community Service / Brian Roelke B-roll, math tutoring -- Project #0271 -- Reel #11, 2001-02-06; cuid19174 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19174)
  - Greenwich Village Montage / Greenwich Village B-Roll -- Project #0404 -- Reel #1, 2004-03-26; cuid19175 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19175)
  - Development Campaign Video / Development Campaign Video MASTER -- Project #0420 -- Reel #59, undated; cuid19176 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19176)
  - Masters in Global Public Health Video for Web / B-Roll of Classroom with Lalitha Ramanthapuram, Ava Chen, Ricardo -- Project #0441 -- Reel #30, 2007-12-06; cuid19177 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19177)
  - NYU Website Videos / B-Roll of Prof. Grier's Physics Lab, Torture Papers, Book Still, Computer B-Roll in Tisch -- Project #0457 -- Reel #16, 2006-03-20; cuid19178 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19178)
  - Stern UG Parents' Weekend Video 2005 / Stern Undergraduate Parents Day Video 2005 (Master w/ Credits) -- Project #0459 -- Reel #12, cuid19179 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19179)
  - All University Commencement 2006 / NYU Commencement 2006 - Edited Program - Dub of DVCAM -- Project #0460 -- Reel #3, 2008-05-01; cuid19180 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19180)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary / Protection Master for the Event (with credits) -- Project #0490 -- Reel #77, undated; cuid19181 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19181)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary / Gloria Coruzzi Lab B-Roll -- Project #0490 -- Reel #115, 2006-10-06; cuid19182 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19182)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary / Classroom B-Roll, Bobst Library, Kimmel, Campus, 1 of 2 -- Project #0490 -- Reel #163, 2008-01-24; cuid19183 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19183)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary / B-Roll of Campus, exterior Silver Center tape 2 of 2 -- Project #0490 -- Reel #164, 2008-01-24; cuid19184 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19184)
  - 175th Anniversary Documentary / NYC NYU Street Scenes B-Roll -- Project #0490 -- Reel #173, 2006-10-06; cuid19185 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19185)
  - 175th Anniversary Video / Compression Shots of Students -- Project #0490 -- Reel #70, 2006-10-16; cuid19186 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19186)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / Orientation Breakfast B-Roll and Dean's Convocation (part 1 of 2) -- Project #0498 -- Reel #1, 2006-08-28; cuid19187 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19187)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / Dean's Convocation (part 2 of 2), Book Signing and Song and Banner -- Project #0498 -- Reel #2, 2006-08-28; cuid19188 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19188)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / Orientation Cohort Breakouts, Orientation Lunch B-Roll and MOS, Staged B-Roll in Gould Plaza -- Project #0498 -- Reel #3, 2006-08-28; cuid19189 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19189)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / Advising Appointment B-Roll -- Project #0498 -- Reel #5, 2006-09-01; cuid19190 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19190)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / Song and Banner Competition (tape 1 of 2) -- Project #0498 -- Reel #6, 2006-09-01; cuid19191 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19191)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / Song and Banner Competition (tape 2 of 2) -- Project #0498 -- Reel #7, 2006-09-01; cuid19192 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19192)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / New Student Interviews in Gould Plaza during Orientation (part 1 of 2) -- Project #0498 -- Reel #8, 2006-09-05; cuid19193 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19193)
  - Stern UG Parents and Family Day Video 2007 / New Student Interviews in Gould Plaza during Orientation (part 2 of 2) -- Project #0498 -- Reel #9, 2006-09-05; cuid19194 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19194)
  - Stern UG Recruitment Video 2006/2007 / Erik Kimel's Chinese Class B-Roll, Santosh Sateesh's Debt Instruments -- Project #0501 -- Reel #10, 2006-12-07; cuid19195 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19195)
  - Stern UG Recruitment Video 2006/2007 / Version 10 v.10 -- Project #0501 -- Reel #30, cuid19196 (Box 224, Betacam sp cuid19196)
  - NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll Package -- Project #0525, undated; cuid19197 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19197)
  - Trustee Pre-Commencement Dinner 2007 / Empire State Building - Violet at Night Beauty Shot -- Project #0532 -- Reel #1, 2007-05-10; cuid19198 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19198)
  - Genomics Building Campaign Video - Dr. Fabio Piano Interview 7/17/07 -- Project #0541 -- Reel #1, 2007-07-17; cuid19199 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19199)
  - Genomics Building Campaign Video - Interview w/ Dr. Michael Purugganan -- Project #0541 -- Reel #2, 2007-07-17; cuid19200 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19200)
  - Genomics Building Campaign Video - B-Roll -- Project #0541 -- Reel #5, 2007-07-17; cuid19201 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19201)
  - Stern MBA Precommencement 2008 / Talent Show - 8/28/2007 -- Project #0548 -- Reel #5, 2007-08-28; cuid19202 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19202)
  - Community Fund 25th Anniversary - 25 Years - NYU Community Fund v.6.0 -- Project #0549, 2007; cuid19203 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19203)
  - Stern UG Pre-Term - Aug 07 / Song & Banner Competition (part 1) -- Project #0551 -- Reel #4, 2007-08-31; cuid19204 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19204)
  - Stern UG Pre-Term - Aug 07 / Song & Banner Competition (part 2), Aliana Costica's Cohort group leaving for lunch -- Project #0551 -- Reel #5, 2007-08-31; cuid19205 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19205)
  - NYU B-Roll Update 2007 -- Project #0523, undated; cuid19206 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19206)
  - NYU B-Roll Exteriors / B-Roll Palladium, Dorms, Silver Center, Welcome Center -- Project #0553 -- Reel #1, 2007-08-16; cuid19207 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19207)
  - Global Network University Video / Singapore Tisch Asia #3 -- Project #0559 -- Reel #10, 2008-03-13; cuid19208 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19208)
  - Global Network University Video / Singapore Tisch Asia #4 -- Project #0559 -- Reel #11, 2008-03-18; cuid19209 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19209)
  - Global Network University Video / Prague (Tape 1 of 3) -- Project #0559 -- Reel #26, 2008-03-18; cuid19210 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19210)
  - Global Network University Video / Prague (Tape 2 of 3) -- Project #0559 -- Reel #27, 2008-03-18; cuid19211 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19211)
  - Global Network University Video / Prague (Tape 3 of 3) -- Project #0559 -- Reel #28, 2008-03-18; cuid19212 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19212)
  - Global Network University Video / Global B-Roll New York City Neighborhoods -- Project #0559 -- Reel #37, 2008-04-02; cuid19213 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19213)
  - Global Network University Video / Prague - B-Roll of students walking around -- Project #0559 -- Reel #44, 2008-04-29; cuid19214 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19214)
  - Global Network University Video / NYU New York Aerials and Miscellaneous -- Project #0559 -- Reel #45, undated; cuid19215 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19215)
  - Global Network University Video / BetaSP Dub of Mini DV Ghana Accra footage (3 of 3) -- Project #0559 -- Reel #46, undated; cuid19216 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19216)
  - NYU B-Roll Update 2008 Master 1 -- Project #0565, cuid19217 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19217)
  - NYU B-Roll Update 2008 -- Project #0565 -- Reel #1, cuid19218 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19218)
  - Stern Undergraduate Precommencement Video 2008 -- Project #0569 -- Reel #4, 2008-04-03; cuid19219 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19219)
  - Dean Tom Cooley Blog Project / Dean Cooley Blog speeches, Greenspan, Paulson (1 of 2) -- Project #0573 -- Reel #1, 2008-04-14; cuid19220 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19220)
  - Dean Tom Cooley Blog Project / Dean Cooley Blog speeches, Greenspan (2 of 2) -- Project #0573 -- Reel #2, 2008-04-14; cuid19221 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19221)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / B-Roll - B Roll B2 -- Project #0578 -- Reel #10, 2008-05-14; cuid19222 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19222)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / B Roll C2 -- Project #0578 -- Reel #2, 2008-05-14; cuid19223 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19223)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / B Roll C3 -- Project #0578 -- Reel #3, 2008-05-14; cuid19224 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19224)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / Graduation University Hall Send Off and Subway B-Roll -- Project #0578 -- Reel #6, 2008-05-14; cuid19225 (Box 225, Betacam sp cuid19225)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / B-Roll - B Roll A1 -- Project #0578 -- Reel #7, 2008-05-14; cuid19226 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19226)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / B-Roll - B Roll A2 -- Project #0578 -- Reel #8, 2008-05-14; cuid19227 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19227)
  - NYU Commencement 2008 / B-Roll - B Roll B1 -- Project #0578 -- Reel #9, 2008-05-14; cuid19228 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19228)
  - Stern Undergraduate Footage 2008 - 2009 / Dean Paul Affuso Construction Walk-thru -- Project #0593 -- Reel #1, 2008-08-29; cuid19229 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19229)
  - Stern Undergraduate Footage 2008 - 2009 / Stern Undergraduate Talent Show -- Project #0593 -- Reel #3, 2008-08-29; cuid19230 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19230)
  - Stern Undergraduate Footage 2008 - 2009 / Motion shots Gould Plaza, Stern -- Project #0593 -- Reel #40, 2009-02-04; cuid19231 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19231)
  - Stern Undergraduate Footage 2008 - 2009 / Stern Campus and village B-Roll -- Project #0593 -- Reel #45, 2009-03-13; cuid19232 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19232)
  - Stern MBA Footage 2008-2009 / Langone Reception -- Project #0601 -- Reel #8, 2009-01-28; cuid19233 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19233)
  - Heymen Center Courses and Interviews / Seminar "Fundraising in Difficult Economic Times" (1 of 4) -- Project #0602 -- Reel #2, 2008-10-15; cuid19234 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19234)
  - Heymen Center Courses and Interviews / Seminar "Fundraising in Difficult Economic Times" (2 of 4) -- Project #0602 -- Reel #3, 2008-10-15; cuid19235 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19235)
  - Heymen Center Courses and Interviews / Seminar "Fundraising in Difficult Economic Times" (3 of 4) -- Project #0602 -- Reel #4, 2008-10-15; cuid19236 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19236)
  - Heymen Center Courses and Interviews / Seminar "Fundraising in Difficult Economic Times" (4 of 4) -- Project #0602 -- Reel #5, 2008-10-15; cuid19237 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19237)
  - Heyman Center Fall 2008 / Naomi Levine Class Presentation -- Project #0604 -- Reel #11, 2008-12-01; cuid19238 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19238)
  - NYU B-Roll / NYU Jin Exteriors B-Roll -- Project #0605 -- Reel #3, 2008-10-01; cuid19239 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19239)
  - College of Dentistry Hudson New York / Hudson, New York B-Roll -- Project #0606 -- Reel #8, 2008-11-18; cuid19240 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19240)
  - Steinhardt Video / B-Roll Footage Percussion Ensemble, Taste of Taiwan Event -- Project #0611 -- Reel #3, 2008-12-03; cuid19241 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19241)
  - Steinhardt Video / Greg in Music Lecture / Thiago in Dr. Melzi Seminar -- Project #0611 -- Reel #4, 2008-12-03; cuid19242 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19242)
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business B-Roll / Exteriors Jan 2010 -- Project #0612 -- Reel #1, 2010-01-27; cuid19243 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19243)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi / B-Roll, Abu Dhabi skyline, waterfront, fishermen -- Project #0613 -- Reel #36, 2009-01-14; cuid19244 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19244)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi / Eli Rosenberg Bosnick Actor's Reading, Garima Vir w/ friends -- Project #0613 -- Reel #44, 2009-02-04; cuid19245 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19245)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi / B-Roll, Garima Vir w/ friends continued, Garmina class -- Project #0613 -- Reel #45, 2009-02-04; cuid19246 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19246)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi / NYU AD Desert Dinner, 4x3 -- Project #0613 -- Reel #79, 2009-10-24; cuid19247 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19247)
  - NYU Commencement 2009 / Commencement 1A -- Project #0619 -- Reel #1, 2009-05-13; cuid19248 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19248)
  - NYU Commencement 2009 / Commencement 2A -- Project #0619 -- Reel #2, 2009-05-13; cuid19249 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19249)
  - NYU Commencement 2009 / Commencement 1B -- Project #0619 -- Reel #3, 2009-05-13; cuid19250 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19250)
  - NYU Commencement 2009 / Commencement 2B -- Project #0619 -- Reel #4, 2009-05-13; cuid19251 (Box 226, Betacam sp cuid19251)
  - College of Dentistry Charles Bertolami Project / NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll 5th Floor Clinic, 11th Floor Simulation Center -- Project #0624 -- Reel #2, 2009-06-02; cuid19252 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19252)
  - College of Dentistry Charles Bertolami Project / NYU College of Dentistry BRoll Lounge, Blue Stone Clinic, Classroom -- Project #0624 -- Reel #4, 2009-06-02; cuid19253 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19253)
  - Jesse Christine Gruman Commencement 2009 / Jesse Gruman Receives Honorary Degree - Commencement 2009 -- Project #0639 -- Reel #1, cuid19254 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19254)
  - NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll 2009 / Commons, Exterior, Lobby, Nexus Collage Close-Ups -- Project #0641 -- Reel #1, 2009-10-26; cuid19255 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19255)
  - NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll 2009 / Rosenthal Institute, Bluestone, Turetsky Wings, Classroom, Rosenberg Wing, Litvall Wing -- Project #0641 -- Reel #2, 2009-10-26; cuid19256 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19256)
  - NYU College of Dentistry B-Roll 2009 / Tarnow Wing, Revisit Urgent Care Suite and Oral Surgery Wing -- Project #0641 -- Reel #3, 2009-10-26; cuid19257 (Box 227, Betacam sp cuid19257)